dj-extensions.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy GDPR

Privacy Policy GDPR 4.0 out of 5 based on 6 votes. 

**This Privacy Policy comes into force on May 25, 2018.**

### Who is collecting your data?

**Your data is collected and controlled by:**

Indico s.c.  
ul. Wałowa 10/3  
84-200 Wejherowo  
Poland  
VAT: PL5882424318

### What data is being collected?

We collect, store, and process the following types of information on our users.

**When you are registering to our site:**

  * Name
  * Username/Password (crypto hashed, never stored in plain text)
  * E-mail address
  * Registered date
  * Last visit date

**When you are purchasing anything on our site we collect billing information:**

  * First and Last name
  * Company name (if applicable)
  * Address
  * City
  * Postal code
  * Country
  * EU Vat ID (if applicable)

**When you are signing up for our newsletter**

  * E-mail address
  * When you visit our website (the newsletter software sends the emails on the times when you most often visit our website to provide you with the best experience and deliver the messages on time)

**When you are using Chat on our website:**

  * Name (when provided, if not provided data is anonymised)
  * IP
  * Last visit time
  * Chat duration
  * Operating system and browser used
  * Web pages (on our site) browsed during open chat

### How are we collecting it?

The personal data is collected by you inputting the data to our website by doing so you are granting us consent/the right to process that personal data in order to provide the service you have signed up to.

Additional personal data is collected by 3rd Parties, for example Salesmanago (online software used for Newsletter), when you receive an email from them, will determine your mail client.

Providing your data is voluntary, however, due to the scope of our services and their specifics it is necessary in order to provide the services we offer.

### Why are you collecting it?

The only reason we collect personal data is to provide the service you are signing up for.

  * Signing up to our website - to let you access downloads section for registered users and allow you later making the purchases on our website (by providing them on later step).
  * Newsletter - to send you updates about our new products, product updates, special offers
  * When making the purchases on website - to collect all data needed by law to process the purchase process.
  * Chat - to let you communicate with our staff to answer questions you may have and provide online support.
  * Helpdesk software (uservoice) - to provide you with the support and answer any questions you may have regarding our products and services by email.

### How are we using it?

We are using your data to provide you best experience when using our website and our services.  
The data will be used for your authentication, debug, collect anonymous stats, and to improve the services we provide.

### Who will it be shared with?

We use processor services to ensure the highest possible quality of service. Your data can be transferred to the following categories (depending on what services you use):

  * electronic payment processors 
  * accounting software
  * google analytics
  * software that supports the newsletter
  * software that supports contact via chat
  * Support software
  * Hosting provider 

We use the services of entities located outside the EU. Your data may be transferred to a third country. We make sure that your data is safe.

You have the option of obtaining a copy of the data. To do this, contact us at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy57293%20=%20'privacy'%20+%20'@';%20addy57293%20=%20addy57293%20+%20'dj-extensions'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy57293%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy57293%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.)[privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com).

Please note that all DJ-Extensions.com data processor providers have been checked to be all GDPR-compliant.

### How long will we store it?

The data will not be processed longer than the purpose for which it was collected.

If you have agreed, your data will be processed until you withdraw consent to their processing.

If you have created an account then your details will be processed until you delete your account.

If a purchase is made on the basis of existing legal provisions, the data will be processed in accordance with the applicable legal provisions, e.g. for accounting and tax purposes.

Chat - your data will be processed until you withdraw consent to their processing or delete your account

Google analytics - data for 90 days

Salesmanago - as long as consent is not withdrawn (you can click “Unsubscribe” in each email)

Uservoice - your data will be processed until you withdraw consent to their processing or delete your account

### What control do I have over it?

If your data is processed on the basis of your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. This does not affect processing until you withdraw your consent.

Consent is provided by our users explicitly when proceeding an action or task (e.g. when they provide user data, contact us using contact forms, sign up to the newsletter, contact us via Chat ).

The only source of data we have is when a user explicitly provides it.

You can always contact us at [privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com) to withdraw any consent and/or to request to delete your account or provide you with the

Our customers rights regarding GDPR are considered and enforced, including:

**Right to be informed:**

In this Privacy Policy we inform our users about the use that will be made of their data

**Right of access:**  
Our users can access all their data stored on DJ-Extensions.com page, by navigating to “My Account” section (after logging in to the site)

**Right of rectification:**  
If you want to change anything in your data just contact ua at [privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com), we'll process all your rectification queries

**Right of erasure:**  
If you want to have your account deleted just contact us at [privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com), we'll process your erasure query within the lawful timescales

**Right to restrict processing:**  
We don't process the data of our customers (and our customers end-users) except as detailed on this page

**Right to data portability:**  
Our users may contact us anytime at [privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com) if they wish to get an export of their personal data as defined under GDPR

**Right to object:**  
We handle all requests on this matter from our users. Our users may contact us anytime at [privacy@dj-extensions.com](mailto:privacy@dj-extensions.com)

### The right to lodge a complaint

If you think that your data is being processed illegally, you have the right to file a complaint with Generalny Inspektor Ochrony Danych Osobowych - [https://giodo.gov.pl](https://giodo.gov.pl/) (in the future the President of the Office of Security)

### Profiling

If you agree to receive the newsletter, we collect your data regarding the activity on our site, e.g. visited subpages and the time of visiting them, and on this basis we choose the time and content of the messages sent. You can unsubscribe from this service by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link in each Newsletter message we send.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.  
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on the DJ-Extensions website.

The website does not automatically collect any information, except for information contained in cookie files.

Cookies files (so-called "cookies") are IT data, described in Directive 2009/136 / EC of the European Parliament concerning the processing of personal data and privacy protection in the electronic communications sector (Directive on privacy and electronic communications) and Article 173 of the Telecommunications Law, in particular, text files that are stored on the Website User's end device and are intended for use of the Website's websites. Cookies usually contain the name of the site where they come from, their storage time on the end device and a unique number.

The entity that places cookies on the Website User's terminal device and gains access to them is the Service Operator - Indico s.c. With the registered office at ul. Wałowa 10/3, 84-200 Wejherowo

Cookies are used to:   
a) adapt the content of the Website pages to the preferences of the User and optimize the use of websites; in particular, these files allow to recognize the device of the Website User and correctly display the site, tailored to his individual needs;   
b) create statistics that help to understand how Website Users use sites, which allows improving their structure and content;

The Website uses two basic types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary files that are stored on the User's end device until logging out, leaving the website or turning off the software (web browser).

“Persistent” cookies are stored on the User's device for the time specified in the cookie file parameters or until the User deletes them.  
In many cases, software used for browsing websites (web browser) allows cookies to be stored in the User's device by default.

Website Users can change their cookie settings at any time. These settings can be changed in particular in such a way as to block the automatic handling of cookies in the web browser settings. They will inform about their every posting on the Website User's device.  
Detailed information about the possibilities and ways of handling cookies are available in the software (web browser) settings.  
The Website Operator informs that changes to cookie settings may affect some of the functionalities available on the Website.  
Cookie files are placed in the user's end device and may also be used by advertisers and partners cooperating with the website operator.  
More information about cookies is available in the "Help" section in the browser's menu.

If the user does not want to receive cookies, he may change the browser settings. We warn you that disabling the cookies necessary for authentication processes, security, maintaining user preferences may make it difficult, and in extreme cases may prevent the use of websites. To manage cookie settings, select the web browser/system from the list below and follow the instructions:

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. One week before changes are applied.
